const json = {
  Q97QyABtNEWjxl_CIYWrmwHypepq4k1ElL_6lzc9HCZUQVYwTUtDUTdOSVVWUk1OSVdKT1lYVU80Ry4u:
    [
      {
        question: "How often do you visit our store?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 1,
        answers: ["I'm a first time visitor"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "What products or services did you purchase during your most recent visit? (Select all that apply)",
        question_type: "mch_b",
        order: 2,
        answers: ['["Musical Instruments"]'],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How satisfied were you with the variety of products available in our store?",
        question_type: "mch_p",
        order: 3,
        answers: ["Very satisfied"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How would you rate the quality of the products you purchased?",
        question_type: "mch_p",
        order: 4,
        answers: ["Very high quality"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Did you find our store layout and organization easy to navigate?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 5,
        answers: ["Yes, somewhat easyÂ "],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How would you rate the friendliness and helpfulness of our staff?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 6,
        answers: ["Average"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Were you satisfied with the overall cleanliness and appearance of our store?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 7,
        answers: ["Average"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How likely are you to recommend our store to a friend or colleague?",
        question_type: "mch_b",
        order: 8,
        answers: ["Very likely"],
      },
      {
        question: "What improvements would you suggest for Aoki Music Store?",
        question_type: "ans_s",
        order: 9,
        answers: ["none"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you have any additional comments or feedback you would like to share?",
        question_type: "ans_s",
        order: 10,
        answers: ["you guys rock"],
      },
    ],
};

const json2 = {
  Q97QyABtNEWjxl_CIYWrmwHypepq4k1ElL_6lzc9HCZUMkdMWDRQSkRCTjMxSDFRNVpXVUs4SlpSTS4u:
    [
      {
        question: "How would you rate the atmosphere of our restaurant?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 1,
        answers: ["Average", "Average", "Very poor"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How satisfied were you with the cleanliness of our restaurant?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 2,
        answers: [
          "Somewhat satisfied",
          "Somewhat satisfied",
          "Very dissatisfied",
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          "How would you rate the knowledge and professionalism of our staff?",
        question_type: "mch_d",
        order: 3,
        answers: ["Average", "Average", "Very poor"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Were you satisfied with the quality and taste of the dishes you ordered?",
        question_type: "mch_p",
        order: 4,
        answers: ["Satisfied", "Satisfied", "Very dissatisfied"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you feel that our menu offers a fair price for the quality of food served?",
        question_type: "mch_p",
        order: 5,
        answers: ["Neutral", "Strongly Agree", "Strongly Disagree"],
      },
      {
        question: "Would you recommend our restaurant to others?",
        question_type: "mch_b",
        order: 6,
        answers: ["Probably", "Not Sure", "Definitely not"],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Overall, how satisfied were you with your dining experience at our restaurant?",
        question_type: "mch_b",
        order: 7,
        answers: [
          "Somewhat satisfied",
          "Somewhat satisfied",
          "Very dissatisfied",
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you have any suggestions for how we can improve our restaurant?",
        question_type: "ans_s",
        order: 8,
        answers: ["none", "none", "no"],
      },
    ],
};
